("Back In Black" by AC/DC)
♪ Back in black ♪
♪ I hit the sack ♪
♪ I've been too long I'm glad to be back ♪
♪ Yes I'm let loose ♪
♪ From the noose ♪
♪ That's kept me hanging about ♪
♪ I've been looking at the sky ♪
♪ 'Cause it's gettin' me high ♪
♪ Forget the hearse 'cause I never die ♪
♪ I got nine lives ♪
♪ Cat's eyes ♪
♪ Abusin' every one of
them and running wild ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm back ♪
♪ Yes I'm back ♪
♪ Well I'm back ♪
♪ Well I'm back back ♪
♪ Well I'm back in black ♪
♪ Yes I'm back in black ♪
♪ Back in the back ♪
♪ Of a Cadillac ♪
♪ Number one with a
bullet I'm a power pack ♪
♪ Yes I'm in a bang ♪
♪ With a gang ♪
♪ They've got to catch me
if they want me to hang ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm back on the track ♪
♪ And I'm beatin' the flack ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna get me on another rap ♪
♪ So look at me now ♪
♪ I'm just makin' my play ♪
♪ Don't try to push your
luck just get out of my way ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm back ♪
♪ Yes I'm back ♪
♪ Well I'm back ♪
♪ Well I'm back back ♪
♪ Well I'm back in black ♪
♪ Yes I'm back in black ♪
♪ Well I'm back yes I'm back ♪
♪ Well I'm back back ♪
♪ Well I'm back in black ♪
♪ Yes I'm back in black ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Take my love ♪
♪ Oh yeah yeah ♪
♪ Oh yeah yeah ooh yeah ♪
♪ Well I'm back ♪
♪ Back ♪
♪ Back in black ♪
♪ Yes I'm back in black ♪
♪ I've hit the sack ♪